<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>ShagunHotel</title>
    <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun" />
    <updated>2019-09-26T21:35:41+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Shagun</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Home</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/home.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/home.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T17:39:55+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <div class="slider-holder"><span id="slider-image-1"></span> <span id="slider-image-2"></span> <span id="slider-image-3"></span>
<div class="image-holder"><img class="slider-image" src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/38/3f98f66901d7de9fa9267fad6bcdbf9b.jpg"> <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/38/3f98f66901d7de9fa9267fad6bcdbf9b.jpg"> <img class="slider-image" src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/38/3f98f66901d7de9fa9267fad6bcdbf9b.jpg" width="2048" height="1365"></div>
<div class="button-holder"> </div>
</div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Wedding Reception</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/wedding-reception.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/wedding-reception.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-18T18:25:21+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/37/wedding-reception-feature-12052016nz1.jpg" alt="" />
                    The wedding reception is the most important event in a wedding. It constitutes the focal point of the whole wedding because it serves as&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/37/wedding-reception-feature-12052016nz1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>The wedding reception is the most important event in a wedding. It constitutes the focal point of the whole wedding because it serves as the common platform for the guests and hosts to come together and sink in the series of fun and merrimentWedding Receptionwith a lavish spread of gourmet cuisine and drinks at their disposal. The whole series of meals to be served at the wedding, be it the evening snacks, scrumptiouscake, dining, late night supper for stay-on guests etc has to be outlined in the invitation card itself so there’s no room for any confusion as to what to expect at the reception. Each and every meal has to be meticulously planned so that there are no unsatisfied guests at the end.</p>
<p>Now, putting the things together to make a wedding reception memorable is painstakingly elaborate and time consuming considered from the angle of a layman. But, it is not so with professional help at your hand. From calculating the cost per plate with accompanied beverages for each meal to the cost involved in laying the tables with decoration for the occasion, we can give you a forecast as to how much you would be spending on each guest apart from a lump sum kept aside for any unseen expenditure. With our rich experience in this line, it’s nothing more than a cakewalk for us to arrange for a flowing wedding reception with all the necessary details thrown in at the right degrees.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Wedding Day</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/wedding-day.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/wedding-day.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-18T20:23:09+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/36/o-INDIAN-WEDDING.jpg" alt="" />
                    The wedding day is the most important day in a person’s life. The future course of a person’s life stands changed after his/her wedding.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/36/o-INDIAN-WEDDING.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>The wedding day is the most important day in a person’s life. The future course of a person’s life stands changed after his/her wedding. So, this important turning point has to be celebrated to the hilt without carrying any emotional, financial, social baggage into the beautiful relationship that is to ensue. To ease out things so that it’s lighter on the pocket as well as on the shoulders we provide some useful suggestions based on our long experience as a wedding planner.</p>
<p><strong class="headcolorRed">The Budget:</strong> The budget for the whole affair has to be set a couple of months before the wedding so that there are no likelihood of unpleasant surprises when the time to pay off arrives. It is usually advisable that all payments are made in advance before the wedding day so that there’s ample time for bargaining and streamlining the whole affair.</p>
<p><strong class="headcolorRed">The Decorations:</strong> The theme for the wedding ceremony has to be decided a few weeks before the big day. Deciding on the theme would help the planners start off from a solid ground.</p>
<p><strong class="headcolorRed">The Clothes:</strong> The clothes meant for the wedding day has to arrive at least a week before the wedding day for proper trials and requisite alterations, if any for an exceptional fitting.</p>
<p><strong class="headcolorRed">The Guest List:</strong> While drawing up the guest list, it is very important to separate the local guests from the outstation guests because outstation guests require more attention for their accommodation etc. involving more costs. Again due care has to be taken to figure out the near exact number of guests who would actually turn up on the wedding day to prevent wastages .</p>
<p>The above mentioned points has to be figured out and accommodated by the clients themselves with guidance from the expert wedding planners wherever needed. Our involvement here ranges from providing the support in choosing the best venue whether it’s a banquet hall, a splendid farm house or a community hall or alike, arranging accommodation for outstation guests, decorations, food caterer and so on. In short, we give you an end-to-end solution for the entire affair where you just prepare yourself for the big day.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Cocktail</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/cocktail.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/cocktail.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-18T20:22:42+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/35/Cocktail-Wallpapers-HD.jpg" alt="" />
                    Cocktail parties add a style statement to any occasion of personal importance. A stag party or a bachelors party is a all male party&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/35/Cocktail-Wallpapers-HD.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Cocktail parties add a style statement to any occasion of personal importance.</p>
<p>A stag party or a bachelors party is a all male party that a would–be-groom throws to celebrate the last day of his bachelorhood. He invites his close friends to reminisce the fun days gone by in their company. Such a party is characterized by boozing and nerve shaking excitement though there are a number of ideas to celebrate this occasion without crossing the boundaries of morality. The first thing that comes to mind about organizing a stag party is the venue. It could be a all male club, a sporting club, or a hotel depending on individual preferences. Secondly, the entertainment element holds the key to a really memorable last night of bachelorhood. Card games, classic Hollywood movies, nerve wrecking DJ Music and wild dance sequences form an ideal background for an entire night of partying. Thirdly, the dress that the host will wear on this occasion will go down the memory lane for all time to come lending the party, style and chic.</p>
<p>But since it remains mostly a western concept, conducting one with the same gusto and elegance requires expert professional handling. Backed by a truly contemporary and efficient list of service providers in this category, we can boast of a truly stylish spread touching on the quality and taste of each drink that would be offered with accompanied refreshments. The key areas like an elegant venue, designer tuxedos, dream inspiring lighting etc are customized part of the deal.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mehndi / Sangeet Ceremony</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/mehndi-sangeet-ceremony.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/mehndi-sangeet-ceremony.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-18T18:53:30+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/34/HinduMiyaanwedding0011.jpg" alt="" />
                    The Mehendi ceremony is considered sacred in almost all wedding ceremonies in India. Here a couple of days before the wedding, the female friends&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/34/HinduMiyaanwedding0011.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>The Mehendi ceremony is considered sacred in almost all wedding ceremonies in India. Here a couple of days before the wedding, the female friends and relatives of the bride get together and smear the bride with a paste of turmeric and sandalwood powder. This is followed by a ceremonial bath after which a person expert in designing Mehendi patterns or the Mehendiwali applies Mehendi on the hands and feet of the bride.</p>
<p>We provide an all encompassing plan to conduct this ceremony keeping with the traditions and practices followed by our clients. From selecting and decorating the venue to going around the whole hog for shopping for clothes, jewellery, arranging professional folk artists for the song and dance accompanying such events, the food on offer etc are attended to in a detailed manner.</p>
<p>Likewise, we provide expert assistance in planning out an outstanding Sangeet Ceremony with all the essential components thrown in at the right proportions.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Tikka/Shagun</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/tikkasagan-ceremony.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/tikkasagan-ceremony.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-18T18:38:31+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/33/magni.jpg" alt="" />
                    One to two days prior to the main wedding day, Tikka/Sagan ceremony is observed in certain North Indian Weddings in lieu of an engagement&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/33/magni.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>One to two days prior to the main wedding day, Tikka/Sagan ceremony is observed in certain North Indian Weddings in lieu of an engagement ceremony. So, it is no less than an engagement ceremony. In this ritual the family members and friends of the bride visit the grooms’ house or a banquet hall to bless the groom. They carry gifts wrapped colourfully for the occasion. Apart from the groom, each member in the groom’ household has something for him/her. The father of the bride or her eldest brother then applies a Tikka on the forehead of the groom and presents him with jewellery like a gold ring or a chain etc.</p>
<p>Thus to make it special we offer all the services necessary to bring together all the ingredients of a traditional Tikka ceremony. The venue, it’s decoration, clothes and jewellery that will pass hands as gifts and blessings are duly attended to so that the bridegroom feels elated at his prospective marriage. We ensure that the gifts packed leave a lasting impression on the recipient. This ceremony also calls for exchange of sweets and dry fruits and you may very well leave it on to us to ensure that the guests get the best taste in the most presentable manner.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Spirtual Tour</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/spirtual-tour.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/spirtual-tour.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-15T19:03:50+05:30</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Tracking</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/tracking.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/tracking.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-15T19:03:40+05:30</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/about-us.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/about-us.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-15T19:03:32+05:30</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ring Ceremoney</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shagun</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/ring-ceremoney.html"/>
        <id>https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/ring-ceremoney.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-18T18:28:41+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/29/wedding-ring_1920x1200_83854.jpg" alt="" />
                    The engagement of a couple prior to their wedding is a very important phase in a relationship. It gives time to the couple to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://shameerpuri.github.io/shagun/media/posts/29/wedding-ring_1920x1200_83854.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>The engagement of a couple prior to their wedding is a very important phase in a relationship. It gives time to the couple to make up their minds about the wedding. Usually a couple of months prior to the wedding, the bride’s and the groom’s family get together at a common venue for this ceremony. The main highlight of the ceremony is the exchange of rings between the bride and the groom. The groom’s ring is procured by the bride’s family and vice versa. The engagement ring is essentially set in some precious metal like gold or platinum with a diamond stud or solitaire. Then the couple is blessed by the elderly members of the family with gifts like clothes, jewelry etc. Unlike earlier days, an engagement ceremony nowadays has attained more prominence by the sheer size and scale of the event. Large number of guests, decorated banquet halls, sumptuous food etc underscore the need for a professional management of this ceremony.</p>
<p class="align-left">Thats where we come into the picture in planning out the whole event without you having to waste your precious time and taking the hassles of running from pillar to post in search of the best deals available to make the ceremony truly glorious. Be it the venue booking or the decorations therein (the engagement ceremony decorations are usually on a low note with soft lights and mild flowers serving the whole purpose) or the food catering and the other basic arrangements from music to photography. Be it an afternoon event or a late evening affair, we make it equally glorious.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
